https://www.silverservice.com/privacy-policy/

Forgot Password
Language:
Currency :
$
€
£
FREESHIPPING ON ORDER OVER $100
Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing industry.
10% OFF THE BILL
Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing industry.
SECURITY PAYMENT
Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing industry.
LIVE SUPPORT
Lorem Ipsum is simply dummy text of the printing industry.
Home> Privacy policy
Privacy Statement
By agreeing to these Terms of Use, you also accept the following Privacy Statement. You agree that the terms of the Privacy Statement are incorporated into these Terms of Use as though set forth in full herein.
Information Collection.
It is our policy that all information provided remain confidential and not be disclosed to any party other than Whitecrest Funding, LLC and its operating partners. We have implemented security measures designed to keep All information you provide to us via electronic or paper form strictly confidential. We will not resell, rent or share the information you provide to us with any unaffiliated third party, except as required by law or, with your consent, to process or evaluate a proposed transaction. We respect your privacy and only intend to use the information you send to us in a responsible and secure manner. This pertains to information collected via application or throughout our due diligence processes.
How the Information is Used.
We use the information we receive about you in order to determine whether your company and its customers will meet our criteria and qualify to enter into a factoring transaction with you and your customers. We may elect to keep the information in order to contact you about new developments at our company whether or not we enter into a factoring relationship.
Updating or Deleting Information
The information you provide can be changed or deleted at any time by contacting us.
Privacy Statement Information
If this Privacy Policy ever changes, we will post a new version on this site and e-mail you a new version. We will provide you with advance notice of any such material change to the e-mail you provide to us except in circumstances where advanced written notice would not be practical. We may seek your affirmative consent to changes in the Privacy Policy for some changes; other changes will be effective unless you stop using the Services. We will clearly state in any notice of change to the Privacy Policy what change is proposed and your choices.
[contact-form-7 404 "Not Found"]
WHAT WE ARE ABOUT Silver Service is a local specialty beverage company headquartered in Centennial, Colorado. Silver Service has proudly served Colorado for 22 years and has developed a reputation for providing the food & beverage industry with the highest quality products, equipment and service.
MORE INFOTerms Of Use
Privacy policy
QUICK LINKSHome
Equipment
Espresso Machine Repair
Equipment Accessories
PRODUCTSCoffee and Espresso
Teas
Follow us on:
facebook
© 2018 Silver Service. All Rights Reserved.
